Time.
This forever?
Isn't this it?
Today, I went in and out all the time because there was no one there.
If it's a romance, it's a romance, if it's a thriller, it's a thriller.
What is the romance thriller genre like?
It's popular. secretly kissing in the room
I really wanted to try this.
So what just happened?
You're missing the thrill, will you get caught or not?
Is no one coming home?
Hey, prestigious mom. Oh, it's a really good idea.
How many people have today’s conditions now?
I don't know, but I think they give it to everyone who is good. Then
I don't know if it's genealogy or not.
So, the senior’s nickname is
This is the end of the rumor.
Live well by losing weight
Are there any?
Are you here? Um, no, that kind of sister is
Why are you like this? Two people
Did you fight again? Hamba
Take a look, thank you.
one. Did you hit it?
Hyunwoo oppa has now drawn a picture of my sister who won’t look down on me.
Why did I not pay attention to Namsik's eyes?
Is it okay? Woohyun.
video.
Oh, what are you doing without sleep for several days?
Well, let's do better now.
But if the accident happens, it's just a dream
I mean, it seems like it. uh.
We are dating, we are dating
I just started dating
Ah.
What is this?
Did you draw it all night? Angiolini
I'm not tired.
Ah, that's because I have no middle ground.
Think about when you like it. I can't even show anything
You couldn't do it. regulations
When I think about it, it just feels like strength.
You're handsome, I'd rather die
Look.
Aww, wow, it's cheap.
Is this how scary love is?
No, Nam Gi-jang also has his own private life, so how can he?
Yes, always? within a three meter radius
Do you want it to be there? No, what kind of brat is always there
Because it was just standing there, right?
Isn't it okay to pass up something in a gaslighting room?
Our Song is always there
I'm getting restless because I'm not standing there.
Why do you keep saying this is gaslighting?
No, this is like a conditioned reflex
Because it is. Ah, to Flanders
To Pavlov, I always
It started with pickup and I was always confused so I told him
I gave him something to eat and then later
Even if you hit me just a little bit, my brother starts drooling
Nam Ki-jeong is the one who is restless right now.
song z. Ah
Seriously, why are you crying? But come on.
Worth it.
But really, why didn’t you come? I told you not to come.
Is this because they caught all the fish? I told them not to come to the reading room.
He might be standing in front, but I stopped him from coming.
zero.
Should I call you? Call me and say something
I'm going to do it, but why am I doing it today?
Are you sitting in front of the school? To do this
It wasn't even in front of the reading room. Yes, to do this.
that's right? Obsessed with princess disease, I am a woman
You will see it. The country is also number one
Are you muttering to yourself like that?
Base and maybe that gourd
While memorizing something like a spell
Are you Dani? Ah, it was an English word.
It was you. Oh why all day
No texts or calls. Did you wait?
You told me not to come to school
Wait, I’m curious as to who will wait.
Calling and texting all the time, that's it.
To the Finns.
What's so dreamy? dream?
hmm.
I mean. cool
I'm going to be a man. No, not that one
A job. Have a good job when you grow up
You have to have it. Everything will be okay already
I was worried, but the penis was still there.
I don’t think I have any thoughts, but you’re stupid, sister.
I guess I can believe it because I have a dream. What I mean is
What I'm saying is that you don't have a dream yet.
uh.
yes. Not yet?
Anyway, right now, my dream is to go to college.
So I think you have that optimistic personality
No. 1 envy. fact
Problems aren't solved by worrying about them. For no reason
Don't get stressed.
Cool, right?
What is your dream?
It's a word. He's going to be a great guy.
But do you really have nothing to worry about?
Anyway, I'm feeling sad.
white powder
Minus Max.
Well, if you look at it like that, what do you know?
Um, are you sure?
You know?
Did you really study? Humans
I can't do it. That's right.
Aren’t our full bellies really amazing? Like this
We study hard every day and we become Korea
It's high school. Study more
Would it be great, or would it be better not to do it?
Or is there something else? Oh, so
Are you going to keep going? Uh, no, no.
three.
This is it.
I'm sorry dad
The top of your foot is also broken.
Don't touch Dad.
P.O says this is a lie.
Well, it goes up to 900,000
Hey Mido, I am
I'm sorry kid
I just said 1 word
I apologize for canceling and studying.
I can’t do it, but I apologize, Kishima.
You guys are liars
Who is the real liar?
Do you know?
Huh, mom?
My mom says that Gyun’s mom is perfect.
They say I'm a poop, so everything I did in the past was a lie
ZE.
Are you a liar?
do. Take turns.
purple. What are you looking at?
Oh, look.
Oh my, is this a face?
Ah, who did this?
Did you hit me? yes. ah.
Isn't it?
You hit me? Calm down, Minho’s mother.
Please wait a moment until you arrive. The child hit me first.
Hey, wow, this is a lie.
Look, where did you learn to lie?
Uh, mom, mom, dad taught me to lie, calm down.
Wait a minute, my mom and dad were busy getting divorced.
Why did you care so much about work?
Mom, don't say things like that.
What? I hit you first?
Oppa, just let someone come and go. Is it now?
Don't worry, he said.
Mom will take care of it, as long as you study hard.
It's okay.
I did something wrong, but that's not right.
Are you doing it wrong? He started the fight first
Let's just ask for the house first.
I want to go home, no, I missed it.
I'm hurt, I need to go quickly, just
Do you want to go home? Are you going to this house?
hmm.
Are you really not going to tell me why you're fighting?
No matter how angry you are, you can't hit me? violence
Is it bad?
Does your sister know?
What?Mom.
Did you lie? Lie.
iced coffee.
Udori as an opponent.
How will they look if I put them to sleep when they haven't done their homework yet?
Just two people walked away. Very stressful
I think I got it.
There's no way he hit me first.
Just look at Minho and his fist comes first
It looks bitter. Mom, it's a lot of talk, who is it?
Use your fist first? Ah, that kind of thing
Where are you? Home education is the problem. Home education is the problem.
Even the stilts are foreigners.
I have to atone, but what should I do?
Kids are usually that big at fighting.
That's right. It seems like that and childish
Let's not call each other like that among adults.
A person who is so good at discerning between interests and interests.
In front of the kids. Divorce and all.
Why did you say that?
I am. I just can't do this
Are you sure you'll skip it?
I like it because it’s ridiculous. It's disappointing
What are you talking about?
Uh, our joke. I
How can you not come home even one day a week?
Mom knows that Jin Lee’s lab is busy, right?
Professor, it would be very difficult if it weren’t for our eldest son.
yes. Still, you need to eat well and take care of your meals.
I love you, son.
okay.
Hello oh
There is no meeting today, right?
I want to increase sales. Ah, promise.
date. date.
Was it that person back then?
Oh, no.
Wow then it changed again
Did I see it?
Only people?
12345678
Row 9
not
It's funny.
Ah, why did we break up this time? I
I told you never to do it.
I asked you to protect just one thing, so why can’t you do that?
uh. No way today
Someone you're dating?
This person.
what?
Because I said I would buy this for you.
so. Even if it's a construction site to make that money
Did you run?
What is this? Yes, thank you
I'll write well.
Are the clothes real?
Do you understand? It's a long term.
That friend from earlier is an art student.
Wow, I feel proud. Seokgu Yoon
Mr.
Our meeting lasts until this time.
No, why suddenly I
I told you not to call me names, right?
That's where our relationship ends, then.
Ah, there. Pyeongtaek City.
yes.
Don’t crack it, Bongnaga. Ah
Yes.
Is it not tasty?No,
But why do you eat it like this?
People also taste bad.
sorry.
Is this what our society is like?
Generation gap. why?
Is it important? do you like me
I don't feel like you're the man.
When you meet people your age, don’t be rude for no reason.
This looks good too.
I'll go first. Yeah, look at that expression for a long time.
It's hard to stay. See you at the meeting.
uh.
sorry. No, Eun-kyung is doing a lot today.
You tell me to do it. So did you just go on a rampage again?
They tell me not to do that, but don’t do that. I take you every day.
I don’t have to give it to you, right?
You are more important to me than work.
More than work. You are number one
It's important.
My friends said they were going to be late again, so let’s go first.
Let's hold hands and go.
Why don't people get married
This is why I do it. Did you not want to break up?
Kijeong, you were earlier.
Some. Hey, I told you I was more important.
I'm honest. for now
I can't speak like you. ah.
Yeah, no, you study less.
I'm not saying it's important.
That's how much studying I have right now
Because it's important. My future depends on it.
Even if it’s not necessarily studying.
It's like drawing a picture of the future with Korea and Japan now.
I never wanted to become a famous model or anything.
Or, I would like to work in a related field.
no. I don't have any?
Are you just working part-time? I told you so.
Even if I don't have to worry about it, I think I'm really cool
It seems like he has become a human.
eww.
Stay still. I'm giving it away,
How to become a great person.
Are you really? You think too much.
I've thought a lot about you too.
It was really hard. I studied it too.
That's not something a real human would do
It worked.
therefore.
Why don't you just leave me alone?
Because you will become a wonderful person.
Is that really true? Of course, right?
uh.
I dreamed it.
Who? Uh.
Who are you? Who are you, my sister’s friend?
This is my younger brother. uh.
Quickly clean up my brother-in-law.
To avoid big trouble
This movie is a thing
No. Because there is.
Oh my, it's me.
Laugh. Martial arts.
uh.
Why are you here? mom now
Are you here? Uh.
huh. How are you now?
Shoes.
Oh, you’re not angry?
Look at this. Also, to my mom last week
You keep doing what you did, right?
Actions become a mirror like this?
Come in quickly. Gudora.
Let’s go together on Saturday.
under.
Just be a kid
No?
He was crying over there. You got a boyfriend, huh?
hmm. Don't you like it?
Break up, no, he came over there. If mom goes, there will be an uproar
Isn't it? See how my older sister fits my mom perfectly
I don't like it. So fast
Break up. well enough
Don't even come to my house.
Don't contact me, don't wait in front of the school.
Why don’t you come to the reading room? For now.
Do that and tell your mom you're done with your name.
No, why are elementary school students the only ones attracting customers?
He's trying to do something like his brother
It's not just elementary school.
I asked. He's obviously ten years old.
Well, he's not just ten years old.
Anyway, just like that.
Oh Yoon-ah, I’ll contact you again. Wooyeonah.
Jo Hyeon-ah. Why are you fighting?
What if I can’t just be an ordinary elementary school student at 9 o’clock?
therefore. hey.
What was there originally in the first election? no like that
You should do it instead of just doing it. Then, secretly, during the first election,
Isn’t that just playing games like this? Right
Play the game by multiplying. Uh, no
Really though.
hey.
It's not broken. Shall I order it for you?
Almost a kid. slightly
Would you like me to take a look? Reporter,
I have something to say?
I can't hear you kid, I'll do it
You have a horse?
Yes, yes.
Look at us hey
Don't answer little friend
Oh, you understand?
Should I buy this?
Don't get that kind of thing. You might end up using strong alcohol.
His name is Nam Gyu-jeong.
that. I'm 18 years old.
This is episode 187, 70. Wow.
Woodrim is one hundred and thirty?
There's no need for that. Where is your school?
Sean What? At the top of the mountain
Is it that high school? Anything?
OK, isn’t our school somewhat famous?
What is it?Where are you going all of a sudden?
There's no need to listen.
Did you eat well?
What the heck, that's a godfather thing.
Hey, didn't you go too far? Ah, on the topic of elementary school students,
So hey, is it our fault that we can't take the test?
Hey, then whose fault is it? ah
ah. uh
Huh? Overdo it.
Don't do it, you're still a top elementary school student.
Did you happen to be right? Hey.
This isn't an ordinary elementary school student, no matter how smart you are now
It's only 3 seconds. you
The doctor only believes in what looks good on the outside and thinks
Even though he looks like an octopus, he is actually kind.
It shows that you are a good person. You cursed me now
It was a compliment, but it seems like an insult, no, that's it now.
Is it important? Oh, is there any way?
brother-in-law
Brother-in-law.
Uh huh?
ah.
uh. ah,
Okay, are you done? uh
this guy.
Desert brother-in-law fun.
is a movie, right.
Kids like teddy bears, not at all.
It works. How are you going to do this? Oh really
Mr. I thought wrong.
Not average enough to listen to classical music
That’s why it has to be like this.
The standard is high, right?
What does Jori like?
Well it's like closure
I like it, why?
Oh, Daewoo asked me
Why Daewoo?
Did the reporter ask you to ask?
It just doesn't work anymore, we can't meet each other
It's okay. You don't know what the emergency captain will say. He's trying to do something.
It seems like it, but just trust it. I keep watching Udol.
It can't go on like this.
Did you memorize it again? From man to man
Let's solve it. It's childish.
Look mom.
What me?
good. great. It should come out like that.
Actually, if I lose, I will break up with my sister.
good.
yes.
ah.
uh. What about a match with Udo?
Let's say we do it.
Do I really have to do that with my elementary school student? me too
I know, elementary school and stuff like that are funny.
But. I want you
I can smile as much as I want for you
You can become an elementary school student. But if you hit it
You said you were going to break up with me, so I can win, right?
I'm not saying this to be rude, but Mudol is 3 years old.
I memorize the capitals of 195 countries around the world.
Oh that. There are only 195
I did it. That is the number of countries in the world determined by the United Nations.
Don't worry. Do I have a plan b?
Plan B. what is that
What do you mean?
Can we just meet secretly?
Oh, that's right, worry about it.
It's not work.
Sorry. These words
Isn't it natural to make people do things that shouldn't be done?
You are special to me, right? Special.
Didn't you know? you mean so much to me
It's so special, so there's no need to worry
Don't worry, leave it to me. trust me
It's strong too.
Why?Did I say something wrong?
No then why?
Say Mapo-gu.
Ugh.
Oh, he came. Oh, he came. Uh, no, evidence evidence.
Ah, the kid was really in a good mood, so I drove him around.
What should I play for you? It's really not going to sour
Really?
Why are you so late? Best
Looks like we haven't met. Why are poopy diapers
I don't like it? I just don't like it, I just don't like it
Where are the crabs? There must be a reason, right? I don't know
I just hate it. He's too tall
My head feels empty and the bill is there
It's a school that only instructors go to.
Only gangsters go there, right?
And that's how you look at people's backgrounds and evaluate them.
No. Anyway, I
I just really, really hate it. And anyway
Mom won't allow it.
Do you like being scolded that much?
Does it matter? Mudori
What if Du takes your sister’s side?
Now, next problem.
EduFigure.
viaduct. Hey
You did it ten minutes ago.
Wow.
He told me to believe it, just wait a minute
Ethiopia is in Africa.
Start with the same country
Ouch.
Sneakers, sneakers.
How about Gongsan after North?
Huh? I understand. Just the remaining three letters from there
Add more.
Addis, Addis.
Addis, amoeba.
North and South. Kijeonga just now
That's why you got mad at me. But why again
Yeah? Well, you did that on purpose. Addis earlier
Didn't you do it in Ababa?
wow really see it
Hit me. What kind of elementary school student
What is the air pressure?
uh. Are you worried about getting drunk again?
There is no truth for elementary school students.
Oh right. Opponent is exhausted
No way.
OY is going this far?
Are you stupid, why didn't you get one question right?
They say the problem lies with the actor. me and i
That's how I thought I was going to get parvo ondal.
I thought you idiot, you manual cheat sheet
What kind of idiot is Perez? He was taller than me.
So I wrote it down here
Look.
Culture is really fun. Handsome but stupid
It's more fun because it's the same. Not yet
It's over, it's over until it's over
No. Isn't that right, kid?
I like Halla so much. That's
It doesn't matter, I'm on your sister's side
What if you become me?
great. last
If you get even one question right.
I'll do it with tears. It's real
Are you really serious? Hey,
Then the last stage.
Where is Jeju Island? Find out me
Do you know? Let's find out eating
I'm sorry, but the bank
You take one first
I can't help it, life is
I think so. Now, the correct answer
Why do you do this? Alalalalalala.
Lalalalalala quickly.
Oppa Paris Paris Han
Please part ways.
This part is real, just for a second
Would you like me to take you on a peace plane just once?
ah?
picture.
I am. Even if some people fall backwards
My nose is broken. Some guy
Even if you fall into the water, you won't find it and the fire will
It's amazing that it doesn't burn even if it sticks.
But kid. That's what kids do,
Is that normal? No,
I also say that such mediocrity is happiness
I want to be happy, I'm happy, yes. Then
My dream is to live in your head for just one day
At that time, I lived with that face for just one day.
Uh huh? Go in carefully, yeah.
Anyway, congratulations on Gomaek winning. But I saw it
I, the popular one, am a good older brother to you.
You don't get along with my sister?
We are already ignored by our mother, bro.
If you meet someone like you, you will be ignored even more.
uh.
They give me advice but it gets ignored.
So for my sister
Please break up.
let's go.
Hey kid, out of your mouth.
Have you seen Karkar?
Was it really fun earlier?
right. What's fun?
Korea seems stupid too, but they did it on purpose.
I thought so? Friends
To make me laugh? 900 million.
It was changed. When I handed it over, the children's names were written in the manuscript.
can come out
ah.
If you read it with a reporter, please contact me.
Choi Jeong-ah, what's going on?
When I saw that there was no contact, I kept giving it to him. where
Aren't you just crying? That's right, Nam Ki-jeong
Nope. Even though I was wet, I made a loud noise and I was like this.
But why the score? Call us.
If it's freezing and the mood gets better, I can eat a hamburger.
Are you writing it? Really
I hope so.
Heejeong, we have a plan B.
Can I meet you secretly?
Ki-jeong. I told you
As special as you are, you are also special to me
You know you’re human, right?
The goddess who goes before us. Are you looking at me?
With a reporter.
So I said something like this and it just
Everything turned upside down and then the kids
He came to me like this and just signed it
Just ask for it together
Is your boyfriend like this? Choi Jeong-ah.
Thank you for not being discouraged for no reason
You were worried. My ears are dying
This is Nam Ki-jong. Mudori says that
Look at that cute thing. You too can challenge me to a duel
You were just trying to play with him.
That's right, right?
But how did you know? Why don't you know?
I'm Song Hyeon. Oh.
He's a voice actor.
Is it because of me that Mudori is doing that?
He says he doesn't want to see me getting scolded by my mom again and again.
If I catch you dating, I'll get scolded again.
Ah, after hearing that, I was a little touched that Woodoli went overboard like that.
Aren’t you angry?
So please understand just a little bit.
Doesn’t Hong get along with my older sister?
But we are already ignored by our mother.
If I meet people, even my brother, I will be ignored even more.
Because people are like me.
ah. Ignore even elementary school students
I got hit and my stomach exploded. all night long
I became that damn pink caterpillar again. What are you groaning for?
By chance, my younger brother cares a lot about culture.
See. Even when I see it, it’s a coincidence
Because it’s a waste of a white board.
Why are you smiling? It reminds me of the first time I saw the rule.
ah. You
So, you're my younger brother. hi?
It's so big.
Are you going to kill my sister?
Do you know?
what? Then when did you two become friends?
From the day you and that guy started dating.
He came to me to ask me to stop him.
First of that day. Truly a brother
I probably called it.
If you stop, you are a good little brother. Be good to me.
I go to class and eat snacks.
Seonho Koo.
Did I completely do everything to him? I don’t even think about it.
B.
Are you saying you don’t believe what you believe?
yes. Who asked?
Please go away.
What should the concept be this week?
Oh, that's what I said last time.
yes.
uh. Where are you going?
In the reading room, lie to meet that brother.
I'm going, no, I'm going to a meeting like that.
Yes. Then me too
Let's go together and what?
Do you know that you are meeting me secretly?
omg.
I'm really sorry. are you okay
Instead, he came and modeled.
Anyone shorter than me is welcome. Tell them to come right away.
Kang Ki-jeong, a meeting to think about going to Spain today.
If you don't go, you won't be able to get to where you've been struggling.
Let's go, the more we go, the further we have to go
It's an opportunity to shake off.
What's wrong? Let's go in and rest. Uh,
If your mother is like Gia,
He told me not to go around and said it was dangerous.
Mom goes into a dark and gloomy place.
I mean it's over.
Then, Master, let me go in.
hmm.
card.
You're pretty. Say hello. Ugh.
I'm mentally ill.
I saw it. Bigfoot is very smart.
how much?
hmm.
Register dogs by color-coded rooms
What do you think? No red and green
I can't, but we all know about Bigfoot.
Larva.
Look at those rooms. Each room has a different color.
How do you feel?
I came here and showed my colors for the first time
Did you find it?
Today is baby blue. It's my sister's room.
You open it.
Dadada.
He came.
huh.
Welcome, kid.
Hmm, I don't know if this is correct. Thank you.
After suddenly coming to the bivouac, they said it was such a nuisance.
I need clothes for a ring. A proper meeting.
No, what are you playing? no, playing
It's not playing, it's playing, right?
Did you say Udol?
What do you think a proper meeting is?
If you invest your time in something worthwhile, well, it's worth it.
What is going on? made the world more developed
Work.
Who decides that?
That's natural. It doesn't matter
Listen up kid, you have value.
You decide what to do yourself. the book
It's not decided, just work hard for a week
Just one day in my life. a special person
So you can draw a picture you like,
That's what it's worth to us. This
It seems like a pretty decent meeting.
You can't admit it. Wear military uniform rather than play
What is more important is the absolute truth. yes
Whether you admit it or not is up to you.
However, we also cannot reject uninvited guests who are rude.
There is freedom.
Wear this or go home
Choose between the two.
What are you doing?
Shall I help you?
hi. I'm Gu Seon-woo.
Aren’t you being too harsh on the kid? kid
He didn't want to be treated like that, so I just treated him like an adult.
sorry. For being so rude
Um, are you okay? Actually, I’m young.
Just save time.
But why are you so upset with your little brother who is full?
Yes, just use the gear
Do it and do it like this
Like this like this
The poor captain is real
Oh?
Actually, this is a bit strange, isn’t it?
I wish I could go back just once.
I'll go again, right?
No, this is it? Still, we
You are ignored by your mother, but when you meet someone like your brother,
There will be more booths.
I think it would be good to beat him, but he is a real opponent.
Take another picture?
Take 5 seconds again?
brother. forward
If you feel uncomfortable, tell them to film again.
Um um hugo.
Is it okay if only the reporter comes now?
Oh right. Regulations and regulations
Ozzy. You said you had withdrawn, right?
When?
First things first.
Let's start like that.
Shall I teach you how to do that?
it's okay?
it's me. Yeah,
I don't know that, don't you know that?
Doyoung just needs to admit it.
Huh? Hey.
Would you like to do something?
Who is this very unpleasant feeling?
Are you sure? Don't have any pictures? That's not yours.
It's better not to draw than to not be able to draw.
It's a waste. Oh, he cried. Still
What about Gorgon? Of course, if you do that for the first time,
Can you do that?
How about drawing it like this?
should. What if I draw that older sister?
Like this? Like this
It's a picture. Have you ever heard of abstraction?
Of course, right? Portraits imitate formations.
Beyond the method of reproduction, the use of dotted lines and planes of color
It is a painting composed of pure formative elements.
If you think of this as a portrait, it can also be a painting.
If it's difficult for you, try drawing it like an abstract painting.
Or, like me, you can just draw the parts you like.
There are no set rules for spoofing.
No matter how you draw, it depends on who draws it.
There is none.
Oh, you can do it. Can you do it?
How about it? Once
Do you want to draw it?
I think this meeting is really strange.
What was it? But let's give it a try.
Next is our little guest.
Uzbekistan Tashkent Romania
Bucharest the capital of Kenya
Nairobi, United Arab Emirates is Abu Dhabi.
Good quality prince pack.
Sao Tome.
Do you have a girlfriend? Uh.
it's hard. If you don't have a girlfriend
What about our eyes? Huh? No
Maybe it's because they decorated it, but it looks pretty when I look at it. Prize money too
Nice and ah. I'm sorry bro
My brother likes someone else
There is.
yes.
You're a hundred times uglier than you would have been by chance. Personality
A thousand times worse. What
Did you do it, because it’s glasses.
Then you said you wouldn't do it.
They give you games, right?
I said it was right.
No, no, stop, stop, do you think I'm stupid? Earlier
I also saw them holding hands. Let’s talk about adult dating. adult
When it comes to dating, it's normal not to be concerned about your ex-boyfriend's monthly schedule.
Why don't I feel like a man to you, how come
I have to say that we like each other.
What I want to find out more and more about
Maybe? I made him hate it because he was afraid his mother would hate him.
That's what I did. I hate discriminatory moms
It's the beginning again, running away. Hitting a wall in a manly manner
Wow. What should I do? stipulate.
Are you going to hate me?
I have a favor to ask.
Please don't do anything to me like a child from now on.
I don't like it? Why?
Is it my heart?
Are you done?